Guide to the Lillian D. Wald Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Henry Street Settlement
  - Financial, donations: Simonton (Box 56, Folder 1.26)
    On Reel 68 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Financial, donations: Wollman (Box 56, Folder 1.27)
  - Financial. Farmers’ Loan and Trust Co. (Box 57, Folder 1.1)
  - Financial, housekeeping account 1924-1926 (Box 57, Folder 1.2)
  - Financial, housekeeping account 1927 (Box 57, Folder 1.3)
  - Financial, housekeeping account: 1928 (Box 57, Folder 1.4)
  - Financial, housekeeping account: 1934 (Box 57, Folder 1.5)
  - Financial, income tax: 1920 (Box 57, Folder 1.6)
  - Financial; Kuhn, Loeb & Co.: 1911-19IS (Box 57, Folder 1.7)
  - Financial; Kuhn, Loeb &. Co.: 1916-1918 (Box 57, Folder 1.8)
  - Financial; Kuhn, Loeb & Co.: 1919-1921 (Box 57, Folder 1.9)
  - Financial; Kuhn, Loeb & Co.: 1922-1923 (Box 57, Folder 1.10)
  - Financial; Kuhn. Loeb &. Co.: 1924-1932 (Box 57, Folder 1.11)
    On Reel 69 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Financial; Kuhn. Loeb &. Co.: statements (Box 57, Folder 1.12)
  - Financial. loans (Box 57, Folder 1.13)
  - Financial, milk accounts (Box 58, Folder 1.1)
  - Financial. National City Bank (Box 58, Folder 1.2)
  - Financial. nursing accounts: 1902-1919 (Box 58, Folder 1.3)
  - Financial, nursing accounts: 1920 (Box 58, Folder 1.4)
  - Financial. nursing accounts: 1921 (Box 58, Folder 1.5)
  - Financial, nursing accounts: 1922 (Box 58, Folder 1.6)
  - Financial. nursing accounts: 1923 (Box 58, Folder 1.7)
  - Financial, nursing accounts: 1924 (Box 58, Folder 1.8)
  - Financial. nursing accounts: 1925 (Box 58, Folder 1.9)
  - Financial. nursing accounts: 1926 (Box 58, Folder 1.10)
  - Financial, nursing accounts: 1930 (Box 58, Folder 1.11)
  - Financial, Nurses' Pension Fund (Box 58, Folder 1.12)
  - Financial, payroll, 1920 (Box 58, Folder 1.13)
    On Reel 70 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Financial, receipt book 1927-1928 (Box 58, Folder 1.14)
  - Financial, receipt book 1928-1929 (Box 58, Folder 1.15)
  - Financial, receipt book: J929 (Box 59, Folder 1.1)
  - Financial. statements: Camp Henry (Box 59, Folder 1.2)
  - Financial. statements: Echo Hill Farm (Box 59, Folder 1.3)
  - Financial, statements: Hamilton House (Box 59, Folder 1.4)
  - Financial, statements: Lincoln House (Box 59, Folder 1.5)
  - Financial, statements: 79th St. Branch (Box 59, Folder 1.6)
  - Financial, loose papers (Box 59)
    On Reel 71 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Folk Festival (Box 60, Folder 1)
    On Reel 72 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Fourth of July celebration, 1927 & 1928 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Game room (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Girls' Work Committee (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Gymnasium (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - "Henry News" (magazine), correspondence (Box 60, Folder 6.1)
  - "Henry News· (magazine). printed material (Box 60, Folder 6.2)
  - Housekeeping class (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Honor Banquet. 1929 (Box 60, Folder 8.1)
  - Honor Banquet. 1930 (Box 60, Folder 8.2)
  - Honor Banquet. 1931 (Box 60, Folder 8.3)
  - Honor Banquet. 1932 (Box 60, Folder 8.4)
  - House rules (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Inquiries, 1924-1926 (Box 60, Folder 10.1)
  - Inquiries, 1927 (Box 60, Folder 10.2)
  - Inquiries, 1928 (Box 60, Folder 10.3)
  - Inquiries, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 10.4)
  - Inquiries, 1930 (Box 60, Folder 10.5)
  - Inquiries, 1931 1 (Box 60, Folder 10.6)
    On Reel 73 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Inquiries, 1931 2 (Box 60, Folder 10.7)
  - Inquiries, 1932 (Box 60, Folder 10.8)
  - Indigence tests (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Legal Committee (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Library, 1926-1927 (Box 61, Folder 2.1)
  - Library, 1928-1929 (Box 61, Folder 2.2)
  - Library, 1930 (Box 61, Folder 2.3)
  - Library, 1931 (Box 61, Folder 2.4)
  - Library, 1932 (Box 61, Folder 2.5)
  - Library, 1933 (Box 61, Folder 2.6)
  - Lists (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Manual training (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Music school, 1920-1926 (Box 61, Folder 5.1)
  - Music school. 1927 (Box 61, Folder 5.2)
  - Music school, 1928 (Box 61, Folder 5.3)
  - Music school, 1929 (Box 61, Folder 5.4)
    On Reel 74 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Music school, 1930 (Box 61, Folder 5.5)
  - Music school, 1931 (Box 61, Folder 5.6)
  - Music school, 1932-1933 (Box 61, Folder 5.7)
  - Music school. Heidi Katz (Box 61, Folder 5.8)
  - Music school. L.D. Harris (Box 61, Folder 5.9)
  - Ninety-nine Club (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Office filing system (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Open House Week (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Playhouse, correspondence: 1915-J917 (Box 62, Folder 1.1)
  - Playhouse, correspondence: 1918-1919 (Box 62, Folder 1.2)
  - Playhouse, correspondence: 1920-1925 (Box 62, Folder 1.3)
  - Playhouse. correspondence: 1926 (Box 62, Folder 1.4)
  - Playhouse, correspondence: 1927 (Box 62, Folder 1.5)
  - Playhouse. correspondence: 1928 (Box 62, Folder 1.6)
  - Playhouse. correspondence: 1929 (Box 62, Folder 1.7)
  - Playhouse, correspondence: 1930-1933 and DO date (Box 62, Folder 1.8)
  - Playhouse. correspondence: Helen Arthur (Box 62, Folder 1.9)
  - Playhouse, correspondence: Eva Fry (Box 62, Folder 1.10)
    On Reel 75 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Playhouse, correspondence: Helen Insersoll (Box 62, Folder 1.11)
  - Playhouse, correspondence: Lewisohn (Box 62, Folder 1.12)
  - Playhouse, correspondence: Morgenthau (Box 62, Folder 1.13)
  - Playhouse, financial (Box 62, Folder 1.14)
  - Playhouse; licenses, construction, etc. (Box 62, Folder 1.15)
  - Playhouse. minutes (Box 62, Folder 1.16)
  - Playhouse, motion picture license (Box 62, Folder 1.17)
  - Playhouse, printed material (Box 62, Folder 1.18)
  - Playhouse, printed material: clippings (Box 62, Folder 1.19)
  - Playhouse, reports and announcements: no date (Box 62, Folder 1.20)
  - Playhouse, reports and announcements: 1917-1923 (Box 62, Folder 1.21)
  - Playhouse, reports and announcements; 1924 (Box 62, Folder 1.22)
  - Playhouse, reports and announcements: 1927-1932 (Box 62, Folder 1.23)
  - Playschool, 1926 (Box 63, Folder 1.1)
    On Reel 76 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Playschool, 1927 (Box 63, Folder 1.2)
  - Playschool, 1928 (Box 63, Folder 1.3)
  - Playschool, correspondence: 1929 (Box 63, Folder 1.4)
  - Playschool. reports, etc: 1929 (Box 63, Folder 1.5)
  - Playschool, 1930 (Box 63, Folder 1.6)
  - Playschool, 1931 (Box 63, Folder 1.7)
  - Playschool, 1932 (Box 63, Folder 1.8)
  - Playschool, 1933 (Box 63, Folder 1.9)
  - Poetry exhibit, 1933 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Pottery (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Printing Press (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Property, alcohol license (Box 63, Folder 5.1)
  - Property, bonding (Box 63, Folder 5.2)
  - Property. general (Box 63, Folder 5.3)
  - Property. 99 Park Avenue (Box 63, Folder 5.4)
  - Property, proposed garage: 318 Henry St. (Box 63, Folder 5.5)
  - Property, prospective purchases (Box 63, Folder 5.6)
    On Reel 77 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Property, 79th Street. (Box 63, Folder 5.7)
  - Property, Staten Island Farm (Box 63, Folder 5.8)
  - Property, 258-60 Henry Street (Box 63, Folder 5.9)
  - Property, 258-60 Henry Street Walton J. Aims (Box 63, Folder 5.10)
  - Property, 258-60 Henry Street Hallock & Sons (Box 63, Folder 5.11)
  - Property, 299-303 Henry Street (Box 63, Folder 5.12)
  - Property; valuation, insurance, taxes (Box 63, Folder 5.13)
  - Loose blueprints (Box 64)
  - Loose photographs and blueprints (Box 65)
  - Publicity. correspondence: 1912-1922 and no date (Box 66, Folder 1.1)
    On Reel 78 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Publicity. correspondence: 1924-1925 (Box 66, Folder 1.2)
  - Publicity. correspondence: 1926-1927 (Box 66, Folder 1.3)
  - Publicity. correspondence: 1928-1931 (Box 66, Folder 1.4)
  - Publicity, films (Box 66, Folder 1.5)
  - Publicity, films: Bray Productions (Box 66, Folder 1.6)
  - Publicity. New York Times (Box 66, Folder 1.7)
  - Publicity; news releases. reports (Box 66, Folder 1.8)
  - Publicity. Organizational Finance Bureau (Box 66, Folder 1.9)
  - Publicity. photographs (Box 66, Folder 1.10)
  - Publicity, printed materials: clippings. I (Box 66, Folder 1.11)
  - Publicity, printed materials: clippings. 2 (Box 66, Folder 1.12)
  - Publicity, printed materials: pamphlets. 1 (Box 66, Folder 1.13)
  - Publicity, printed materials: pamphlets, 2 (Box 66, Folder 1.14)
  - Publicity, Henry Powers Story (Box 66, Folder 1.15)
    On Reel 79 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Rebecca Schatz Memorial Fund. 1 (Box 66, Folder 2.1)
  - Rebecca Schatz Memorial Fund. 2 (Box 66, Folder 2.2)
  - Rebecca Schatz Memorial Fund, Jane E. Hitchcock (Box 66, Folder 2.3)
  - Reference, letters of introduction: 1909-1916 (Box 67, Folder 1.1)
  - References, letters of introduction: 1917-1918 (Box 67, Folder 1.2)
  - References. letters of introduction: 1919-1922 (Box 67, Folder 1.3)
  - References, letters of introduction: 1923 (Box 67, Folder 1.4)
  - References. letters of introduction: 1924-1925 (Box 67, Folder 1.5)
  - References, letters of introduction: 1926 (Box 67, Folder 1.6)
  - References, letters of introduction: 1921 (Box 67, Folder 1.7)
  - References, letters of introduction: 1928 (Box 67, Folder 1.8)
  - References. letters of introduction: 1929 (Box 67, Folder 1.9)
  - References. letters of introduction: 1930 (Box 67, Folder 1.10)
  - References. letters of introduction: 1931 (Box 67, Folder 1.11)
    On Reel 80 of the Wald Microfilm
  - References. letters of introduction: 1932 (Box 67, Folder 1.12)
  - References. letters of introduction: 1933-1936 (Box 67, Folder 1.13)
  - Senior Organization (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Social Activities Committee: no date (Box 67, Folder 3.1)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1921 (Box 67, Folder 3.2)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1922 (Box 67, Folder 3.3)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1923-1925 (Box 67, Folder 3.4)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1926 (Box 67, Folder 3.5)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1921 (Box 67, Folder 3.6)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1928 (Box 67, Folder 3.7)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1929 (Box 67, Folder 3.8)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1930 (Box 67, Folder 3.9)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1931 (Box 68, Folder 1.1)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1932 (Box 68, Folder 1.2)
  - Social Activities Committee: 1933 (Box 68, Folder 1.3)
    On Reel 81 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Speaking engagements (Bertha B. Carter) (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Staff correspondence. A (Box 68, Folder 3.1)
  - Staff correspondence, Ethel Aarons (Box 68, Folder 3.2)
  - Staff correspondence. B (Box 68, Folder 3.3)
  - Staff correspondence, Ruth Becker (Box 68, Folder 3.4)
  - Staff correspondence, Beryl A. Black (Box 68, Folder 3.S)
  - Staff correspondence, Marion Blacker (Box 68, Folder 3.6)
  - Staff correspondence, Mary Jane Brown (Box 68, Folder 3.7)
  - Staff correspondence. C (Box 68, Folder 3.8)
  - Staff correspondence. Dorothy Caffin (Box 68, Folder 3.9)
  - Staff correspondence, Ruth Canfield (Box 68, Folder 3.10)
  - Staff correspondence, Robert Cardwell (Box 68, Folder 3.11)
  - Staff correspondence. Bertha Carter (Box 68, Folder 3.12)
    On Reel 82 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Staff correspondence. Florence Clark (Box 68, Folder 3.13)
  - Staff correspondence. Kathleen Cockburn (Box 68, Folder 3.14)
  - Staff correspondence, Mabel Coleman (Box 68, Folder 3.15)
  - Staff correspondence. Viola Percy Conklin (Box 68, Folder 3.16)
  - Staff correspondence. John Cornehlsen (Box 68, Folder 3.17)
  - Staff correspondence. Paul and Ada Cornil (Box 68, Folder 3.18)
  - Staff correspondence. D (Box 69, Folder 1.1)
  - Staff correspondence. Mabel Curran de Bonneval (Box 69, Folder 1.2)
  - Staff correspondence. Clementine de Rocco (Box 69, Folder 1.3)
  - Staff correspondence, Naomi Deutsch (Box 69, Folder 1.4)
  - Staff correspondence, I.J. Domas (Box 69, Folder 1.5)
  - Staff correspondence. Isabel Dwight (Box 69, Folder 1.6)
  - Staff correspondence. E (Box 69, Folder 1.7)
  - Staff correspondence. F (Box 69, Folder 1.8)
  - Staff correspondence, G (Box 69, Folder 1.9)
    On Reel 83 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Staff correspondence. Elizabeth T. Gale (Box 69, Folder 1.10)
  - Staff correspondence. Earle Gatchell (Box 69, Folder 1.11)
  - Staff correspondence. Helen W. Gausse (Box 69, Folder 1.12)
  - Staff correspondence. Anne Elizabeth Geddes (Box 69, Folder 1.13)
  - Staff correspondence. Anne W. Goodrich (Box 69, Folder 1.14)
  - Staff correspondence. H (Box 69, Folder 1.15)
  - Staff correspondence. Georgia Coyle Hall (Box 69, Folder 1.16)
  - Staff correspondence. Alice G. Heap (Box 69, Folder 1.17)
  - Staff correspondence. Olga Hennoch (Box 69, Folder 1.18)
  - Staff correspondence. Edgar W. Herbert (Box 69, Folder 1.19)
  - Staff correspondence. Elsa H. Herrmann (Box 69, Folder 1.20)
  - Staff correspondence. Karl D. Hesley (Box 69, Folder 1.21)
  - Staff correspondence, Jane Elizabeth Hitchcock (Box 69, Folder 1.22)
  - Staff correspondence. Laura Hunt (Box 69, Folder 1.23)
  - Staff correspondence. Vera E. Hunt (Box 69, Folder 1.24)
  - Staff correspondence, I (Box 69, Folder 1.25)
  - Staff correspondence, .J (Box 69, Folder 1.26)
  - Staff correspondence. Rosa Jessen (Box 69, Folder 1.27)
    On Reel 84 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Staff correspondence. K (Box 69, Folder 1.28)
  - Staff correspondence. Willard L. Kauth (Box 69, Folder 1.29)
  - Staff correspondence, Priscilla Kimball (Box 69, Folder 1.30)
  - Staff correspondence. Harriet Knight (Box 69, Folder 1.31)
  - Staff correspondence. L (Box 70, Folder 1.1)
  - Staff correspondence, Samuel Lowenkron [Lowe] (Box 70, Folder 1.2)
  - Staff correspondence, M (Box 70, Folder 1.3)
  - Staff correspondence, Mc (Box 70, Folder 1.4)
  - Staff correspondence. N (Box 70, Folder 1.5)
  - Staff correspondence. O (Box 70, Folder 1.6)
  - Staff correspondence. P (Box 70, Folder 1.7)
  - Staff correspondence, Julius Portnoy (Box 70, Folder 1.8)
  - Staff correspondence. R (Box 70, Folder 1.9)
    On Reel 85 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Staff correspondence, Bonnie Reeves (Box 70, Folder 1.10)
  - Staff correspondence, Helen Riggs (Box 70, Folder 1.11)
  - Staff correspondence, Robert Rubin (Box 70, Folder 1.12)
  - Staff correspondence, S-Si (Box 70, Folder 1.13)
  - Staff correspondence. Sm-Sz (Box 70, Folder 1.14)
  - Staff correspondence, Betty Simonton (Box 70, Folder 1.15)
  - Staff correspondence, T (Box 70, Folder 1.16)
  - Staff correspondence. U-V (Box 70, Folder 1.17)
  - Staff correspondence. W (Box 71, Folder 1.1)
    On Reel 86 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Staff correspondence. Marguerite A. Wales (Box 71, Folder 1.2)
  - Staff correspondence, Gladys Weatherly (Box 71, Folder 1.3)
  - Staff correspondence. Beulah Weldon (Box 71, Folder 1.4)
  - Staff correspondence. Wile family (Box 71, Folder 1.5)
  - Staff correspondence, Audrey Wright (Box 71, Folder 1.6)
  - Staff correspondence, Y (Box 71, Folder 1.7)
  - Staff correspondence, miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 1.8)
  - Staff applications, no date (Box 71, Folder 2.1)
  - Staff applications, 1922 (Box 71, Folder 2.2)
  - Staff applications, 1924-1925 (Box 71, Folder 2.3)
  - Staff applications, 1926 1 (Box 71, Folder 2.4)
  - Staff applications, 1926 2 (Box 71, Folder 2.5)
  - Staff applications, 1927 1 (Box 71, Folder 2.6)
  - Staff applications, 1927 2 (Box 71, Folder 2.7)
  - Staff applications, 1928 1 (Box 71, Folder 2.8)
    On Reel 87 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Staff applications, 1928 2 (Box 71, Folder 2.9)
  - Staff applications, 1929 1 (Box 71, Folder 2.10)
  - Staff applications, 1929 2 (Box 71, Folder 2.11)
  - Staff applications, 1930 1 (Box 72, Folder 1.1)
  - Staff applications, 1930 2 (Box 72, Folder 1.2)
  - Staff applications, 1930 3 (Box 72, Folder 1.3)
  - Staff applications, 1931 (Box 72, Folder 1.4)
    On Reel 88 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Staff applications, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 1.5)
  - Staff applications, 1933 (Box 72, Folder 1.6)
  - Staff, lists (Box 72, Folder 1.7)
  - Staff meetings: memoranda. notices, correspondence (Box 72, Folder 1.8)
  - Staff meetings: minutes, 1919-1926 (Box 72, Folder 1.9)
  - Staff meetings: minutes. 1927 (Box 72, Folder 1.10)
  - Staff meetings: minutes, 1928 (Box 72, Folder 1.11)
  - Staff meetings: minutes. 1930 (Box 72, Folder 1.12)
  - Staff meetings: minutes, 1931 (Box 72, Folder 1.13)
  - Staff meetings: minutes. 1932 (Box 72, Folder 1.14)
  - Staff meetings: minutes. 1933 (Box 72, Folder 1.15)
  - Staftime study (Box 72, Folder 1.16)
  - Summer work (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Thanksgiving Day parties (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Visitors: 1 (Box 72, Folder 4.1)
  - Visitors: 2 (Box 72, Folder 4.2)
    On Reel 89 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Miscellaneous items: (Box 73)
    - Pocket notebook (containing personal names and names of social services agencies) (Box 73)
    - Address-book (Westport, CT, Callers List, names and phone numbers) (Box 73)
    - Day calendar (appointment book, 1931) (Box 73)
    - Clippings (not filmed) (Box 73)
  - Contain Miss Wald's personal book collection and were not filmed. (Box 74-78)
  - Index cards, 1: B-Gi (Box 79)
    On Reel 90 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Index cards,2: Gi-Pe (Box 80)
    On Reel 91and 92 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Index cards. 3: Pe-Z (Box 81)
    On Reel 92 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Index cards, 3: Pe-Z (Box 81)
    On Reel 93 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Index cards, 3: miscellaneous (Box 81)
- Series VI: Labor Relations
  - General, correspondence (Box 82, Folder 1.1)
  - General; memoranda. reports. etc. (Box 82, Folder 1.2)
  - General, printed materials (Box 82, Folder 1.3)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation. correspondence: 1915-1916 (Box 82, Folder 2.1)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation, correspondence: 1917-1918 (Box 82, Folder 2.2)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation, correspondence: 1919-1920 (Box 82, Folder 2.3)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation. correspondence: 1921-1922 (Box 82, Folder 2.4)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation. correspondence: 1923-1925 (Box 82, Folder 2.5)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation. correspondence: 1926-1927 (Box 82, Folder 2.6)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation. correspondence: 1928 (Box 82, Folder 2.7)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation, correspondence: 1929 (Box 82, Folder 2.8)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation, correspondence: 1930 (Box 82, Folder 2.9)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation. health insurance: correspondence (Box 82, Folder 2.10)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation. health insurance: memoranda. Minutes (Box 82, Folder 2.11)
  - American Association for Labor Legislation. health insurance: printed materials (Box 82, Folder 2.12)
    On Reel 94 of the Wald Microfilm
  - American Association for Labor Legislation. Workmen's Compensation (Box 82, Folder 2.13)
  - Arsenal Employees Experiment (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Unemployment Relief Committee (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Work Bureau. 1930 (Box 82, Folder 6.1)
  - Emergency Work Bureau. 1931 (Box 82, Folder 6.2)
  - Emergency Work Bureau, 1932 (Box 82, Folder 6.3)
  - Emergency Work Bureau, 1933 (Box 82, Folder 6.4)
  - Emergency Work Bureau, Red Cross food tickets (Box 82, Folder 6.5)
  - Employment agencies (Box 83, Folder 1)
    On Reel 95 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Government conference, 1919 report (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Committee reports (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - International Congress of Working Women (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Labour Party (England) (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Legislation (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - New York State, Commissioner of Labor: appointment of Frances Kelley (Box 83, Folder 7.1)
  - New York State, Factory Investigating Commission (Box 83, Folder 7.2)
  - Strikes, miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 8.1)
  - Strikes, Chicago (Box 83, Folder 8.2)
  - Strikes, Cleveland Cloakmakers’ Union (Box 83, Folder 8.3)
  - Strikes. Coal Miners (Box 83, Folder 8.4)
  - Strikes: Danville, Virginia Textile Workers (Box 83, Folder 8.5)
  - Strikes: Lawrence, Massachusetts Textile Workers (Box 83, Folder 8.6)
  - Strikes, New York Garment Workers: correspondence (Box 83, Folder 8.7)
  - Strikes, New York Garment Workers: printed materials (Box 83, Folder 8.8)
  - Strikes~ New York Paper Box Makers (Box 83, Folder 8.9)
  - Strikes. Passaic Textile Workers (Box 83, Folder 8.10)
    On Reel 96 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Strikes, Pullman Porters (Box 83, Folder 8.11)
  - Strikes: Troy, New York Laundries (Box 83, Folder 8.12)
  - Tenement Home Work (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Union Health Center (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Unions (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Women's Trade Union League. no date (Box 83, Folder 12.1)
  - Women's Trade Union League, 1904-1907 (Box 83, Folder 12.2)
  - Women's Trade Union League, 1908-1920 (Box 83, Folder 12.3)
  - Women's Trade Union League, 1922-1928 (Box 83, Folder 12.4)
  - Women's Trade Union League, 1929-1931 (Box 83, Folder 12.5)
  - Workmen's Theatre (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Series VII: Nursing
  - General, correspondence (Box 84, Folder 1.1)
  - General. reports and printed materials (Box 84, Folder 1.2)
  - Army nurses, government insurance (Box 84, Folder 2.1)
  - Army nurses, military rank (Box 84, Folder 2.2)
  - Army School of Nursing (Red Cross). correspondence (Box 84, Folder 3.1)
  - Army School of Nursing (Red Cross); reports, accounts. etc. (Box 84, Folder 3.2)
  - Canada (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - China, Yamai Kin (Box 84, Folder 5.1)
  - China, Hsui Lan Poi (Box 84, Folder 5.2)
  - China. Zingling Tai (Box 84, Folder 5.3)
  - Cost-pet-visit (Box 84, Folder 6)
    On Reel 97 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Florence Nightingale Memorial Celebration, correspondence (Box 84, Folder 7.1)
  - Florence Nightingale Memorial Celebration, printed materials (Box 84, Folder 7.2)
  - Harmon Foundation, 1926 (Box 84, Folder 8.1)
  - Harmon Foundation, 1927 (Box 84, Folder 8.2)
  - Harmon Foundation, 1928 (Box 84, Folder 8.3)
  - Harmon Foundation. 1929 (Box 84, Folder 8.4)
  - Harmon Foundation, 1930 (Box 84, Folder 8.5)
  - Home instruction (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Legislation (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Nursing experiences (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Publications (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - "The Public Health Nurse" (magazine) (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Public health nursing, correspondence (Box 85, Folder 4.1)
  - Public health nursing; memoranda. reports, etc. (Box 85, Folder 4.2)
  - Public health nursing. printed materials (Box 85, Folder 4.3)
    On Reel 98 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Public health nursing, National Organization for Public Health Nursing (Box 85, Folder 4.4)
  - Public health nursing; Rockefeller Foundation, correspondence (Box 85, Folder 4.5)
  - Public health nursing; Rockefeller Foundation, reports (Box 85, Folder 4.6)
  - Registration of nurses (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Training, correspondence (Box 85, Folder 6.1)
  - Training, printed materials (Box 85, Folder 6.2)
  - Visiting Nurse Service. general correspondence: 1916 (Box 85, Folder 7.1)
  - Visiting Nurse Service, general correspondence: 1918 (Box 85, Folder 7.2)
  - Visiting Nurse Service. general correspondence: 1919 (Box 85, Folder 7.3)
  - Visiting Nurse Service. general correspondence: 1920-1926 (Box 85, Folder 7.4)
  - Visiting Nurse Service. general correspondence: 1927-1928 (Box 85, Folder 7.5)
  - Visiting Nurse Service, general correspondence: J929-1932 and no date (Box 85, Folder 7.6)
  - Visiting Nurse Service, general correspondence: Christine Anderson (Box 85, Folder 7.7)
  - Visiting Nurse Service, general correspondence: Mabel Coleman (Box 85, Folder 7.8)
  - Visiting Nurse Service, general correspondence: Bertha Franz (Box 85, Folder 7.9)
  - Visiting Nurse Service, general correspondence: Stella Akulin Koenig (Box 85, Folder 7.10)
  - Visiting Nurse Service, Association Plan (Box 86, Folder 1.1)
    On Reel 99 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Visiting Nune Service, Committee of 100 (Box 86, Folder 1.2)
  - Visiting Nune Service, donations (Box 86, Folder 1.3)